Robot IR Control

EN:
Simple remote control for iClebo Arte, Pop and Omega vacuum cleaner by IR
---
Tool for remote control Your iClebo™ Arte, Pop or Omega robot cleaner from smartphone with IR. You can use this application when the original remote is not nearby or if you lost it.

RU:
Пульт для управления роботом-пылесосом iClebo Arte, Pop и Omega по ИК
---
Пульт дистанционного управления роботом-пылесосом iClebo™ Arte, Pop или Omega для телефонов с IR излучателем. Вы сможете управлять роботом когда оригинального пульта нет под рукой, сели батарейки или Вы вообще его потеряли.

KR:
IR를 가진 당신의 전화에서 iClebo 로봇 원격 제어
---
원격 제어를 위한 공구 IR를 가진 smartphone에서 iClebo™ Arte, Pop 또는 Omega 로봇 세탁 기술자 래 지 않거나 분실 했을 때이 응용 프로그램을 사용할 수 있습니다.
